{
  "questions": [
    {
        "id" : "1" , 
        "question": "Java is a high-level language.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True",
        "Explanation": "Java is a high-level language because it is more easily understood by humans, Low=-level languages are always static."
    },
    {
        "id" : 2,
        "question": "What kind of language is java?",
        "options": [
            "Functional Language",
            "Procedural Language",
            "Object-Oriented Language",
            "Structured Language"
        ],
        "answer": "Object-Oriented Language",
        "Explanation": "Java is an Object-Oriented Language."
        
    },
    {
        "id" : 3,
        "question": "What is the result of 24 % 5? ",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "4.8",
            "24"
        ],
        "answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "% finds the remainder of an expression, the remainder of 24/5 being 4"
        
    },
    
    {
        "id" : 4,
        "question": "What is the default value of an integer?",
        "options": [
            "Null",
            "0",
            "Not Assigned",
            "1"
            ],
        "answer": "0",
        "Explanation": "When an integer is called and not defined, the default value is 0"
    },
    {
        "id" : 5,
        "question": "What is the default value of an object?",
        "options": [
            "Null",
            "0",
            "Not Assigned",
            "1"
            ],
        "answer": "Not Assigned",
        "Explanation": "When an object is not defined, the default value is Not Assigned"
    },
    {
        "id" : 6,
        "question": "Is it possible to have multiple classes in the same java file?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
            ],
        "answer": "Yes",
        "Explanation": "It is possible to have multiple classes in the same java file."
    },
    {   
        "id" : 7,
        "question": "What does multiple inheritance mean?",
        "options": [
            "Multiple classes inheriting from more super classes",
            "Multiple classes inheriting from one super class",
            "One class inheriting from multiple super classes",
            "None of the above"
            ],
        "answer": "One class inheriting from multiple super classes",
        "Explanation": "Multiple inheritance in java allows for one class to inherit from multiple super classes."
    },
    {
        "id" : 8,
        "question": "What is the process that involves recognizing and focusing on the important characteristics of a situation or object is known as",
        "options": [
            "Encapsulation",
            "Polymorphism",
            "Abstraction",
            "None of the above"
            ],
        "answer": "Abstraction",
        "Explanation": "Abstraction is the process that involves recognizing and focusing on the important characteristics of a situation or object."
    },
    {
        "id" : 9,
        "question": "Is it possible to change the length of an array after it is made?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
            ],
        "answer": "No",
        "Explanation": "Arrays are static length."
    },
    {
        "id" : 10,
        "question": "Is it possible to change the length of an arraylist after it is made?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
            ],
        "answer": "Yes",
        "Explanation": "Arraylists are not static in length."
    }
    
  ],
  
  "quiz": {
    "total_questions": 10,
    "time": 30
  }
}
